Guide to the William S. Johnson Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers
  - Bound volume: University of Wisconsin. Notebook #3. W. S. Johnson. Dept. of Chemistry. (Nov. 1, 1940-May 29, 1942) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bound volume: Leopold Ruzicka (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bound volume: The First International Kyoto Conference on New Aspects of Organic Chemistry (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Bound volume: Stanford University Toxic Gas User's Handbook (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Bound volume: Robert Burns Woodward and the Art of Organic Synthesis (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Reprints; abstracts, notes, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Bound volume: grant application (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Bound volume: NSF proposal (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Reprints, notes, photocopies, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Reprints, notes, photocopies, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Reprints, notes, photocopies, correspondence (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Personal letters: Johnson 1st Annual Symposium 1986 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Records of Oct. '89 shoulder surgery (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Johnson 1st Annual Symposium 1986 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Medical insurance (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Zoecon Corporation (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Chemistry Dept. postdoc listing; appendices for unidentified paper (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis via Acetal Templates VI. A Key Intermediate for the Total Synthesis of Vitamin D Types. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Grant applications (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Sterling-Winthrop Cyclization Studies (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry 120 (1) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Articles referring to 17a,21- cyclic orthoesters (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Winthrop (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - 16,17-Dehydroprogesterone--Commercial development (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Robinson's steroid syntheses (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Du Pont (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Du Pont--Consultant, 1946-1948 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - article photocopy; legal document: Warner-Lambert v. Glaxo (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Warner-Lambert v. Glaxo: Service charges and expenses (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Legal document; correspondence; notes on index cards (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Archer (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Johnson Symposium 1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, article photocopy (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Organon (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Stanford University miscellaneous correspondence (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Trost, Barry National Medal of Science (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Trost, Barry (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Material re: Medal of Science. photographs (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Johnson Tetrahedron Prize (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - ChemDraw booklet & license agreement (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Talk on April 5. '92 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Articles; NSF proposals (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Bartlett, Ted: autobiography (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Trost, Barry Material; ChemDraw License Agreement (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Stanine MS and Conrow MS; Tet let. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Carboalkoxyallylsilane Terminator for Biomimetic Polyene Cyclizations. A Route to 21-Hydroxyprogesterone Types. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Assymetrical Synthesis article correspondence (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tetrahedron draft: Choi et al. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis…13. Preparation of Aldol Compounds from Butane 1,3-diol Acetals. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Concomitant Formation of Four Rings in a Biomimetic Polyene Cyclization to Produce the Steroid Nucleus (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - 10. Aldol-Type Reactions. Preparation of a Nonactic Acid Intermediate. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis…15. The Preparation of Enantiomerically Pure Mevinolin Analogs (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Daniel's Paper (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Reactions with Organometallic Reagents (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Dihydromyoporone; Still's materials (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - 9. Further Studies of the Allylation Raction. Preparation of (-)-Dihydromyoporone. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - A Highly Stereoselective Route to Calcitriol Lactone (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Lipoic Acid (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Synthesis of Euphol and Tirucallol (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis via Acetal Templates V. Reactions with Cyanotrimethylsilane. Enantioselective Preparation of Cyanohydrine and Derivatives. (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis via Acetal Templates III. On the Stereochemistry Observed in the Cyclization of Chiral Acetals of Polyolefinic Aldehydes; Formation of Optically Active Homoallylic Alcohols (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Asymmetric Synthesis via Acetal Templates IV. Reactions with Sylylacetylenic Compounds. Formation of Chiral Porparygylic Alcohols (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Juvenile Hormone (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Cholestanones (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - ORD curves (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Synthesis of Delta1-Cholestene. W. Hoffman. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Mechanism of Allylic Cylc. X. Neustaedter et al. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Veratrum Alkaloids (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Olefin Cycl. Reprints. Johnson, Bartlett. (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Pentacyclic Triterpenoids (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Olefinic Ketal Claisen. J. H. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - B/C Config. of Veratramine and Jervine. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Okamura, William Material (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Pentacyclic Friterpenoids: Joint--Ireland and Johnson (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Acetylenic Bond Participatopm etc. I, II and III (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Discussion with Organon, Jun. 7-10, 1974 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Roussel Prize--correspondence, etc. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Flory, Paul (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Flory, Paul (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bunch, Marlene K. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Stork, Gilbert (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Foley, Anne S. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Breslow, Ronald (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Spencer, Thomas A., Jr. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, slides (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Typescripts, magazines, correspondence (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Biographical Material (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Binder with research proposal (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Binder with research proposal (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Research proposal (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Seeman--autobiographies (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - NSF Prop. 83--Original (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Wilcox, Craig Material (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Phenylacetylne Terminator Discussion (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Hi End stereo systems (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - X-ray; R. Kullnig, RPI (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Satellite (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Tribble Control Program (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Alcon--Conrow; Samples=grant (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Mechanism: Erizynatic Cyclizat. of epoxide (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Tests: Hydroxypiperidine Derivative A (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Griffin-Johnson Project (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - LeNoble - Pressure Cyclization (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Mechanism of Polyenic Cyclization (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Benvenste Joint Publication (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Rich, Dan Project and statine work (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - X-ray. Tandem Products. U. Schubert. (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Revised C-S paper (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - A New Concept for Improving Biomimetic Polyene Cyclizations (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Synergists--Rate Enhancement. Lindell-Steele. (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Review Articles. C and EN; Chemtracts. (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Statine--Full Paper (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Acetal Review Article (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Opt. Actine J.H. (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Experiments for Garst-Cheung (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Garst-Cheung Cyclizations (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Experimental Section & Tables; Hall's Bromide (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Longifolene (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Cortexolone (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - A-pinene (Mosher) (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Stephenson Project (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Phenylacetylene Terminator Discussion (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Phenylacetylene Terminator (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Carlson, Janet. p-ockz phenylacetylene terminator (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Carlson, Janet. p-Fluorophenylacetylene terminator (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Carlson, Janet. phenyl acetylene terminator (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Ward, Carl. Phenylacetylene terminator (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Total Asymmetric Synth of 11A OH progesterone. LAH-Darvon alc reduction. (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Journal of the American Chemical Society (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Journals for Sale (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Journal of the American Chemical Society reprints (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Solicitation of Industrial Grants (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Lilly Negotiations (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Aldrich (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Solicitations of Industrial Funds, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Safety (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Lecture and Other Current Commitments (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Lecture correspondence (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Johnson Symposium 1993 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Publications Lists, Johnson, JD Roberts (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Johnson Biographical Material (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Cellular Phone (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Academic Positions in Other Chemistry Departments--Current (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - GC and HPLC equipment (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Postdoc Students (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Telephone (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Hydroxylation of dl-Cortexolone C. J. Sih (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - List of Johnson Graduate Students (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Table Ronde Roussel 1978 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Tetrahedron (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Personal Involvements (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Synthesis (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Material for Posting (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Special Patent Matters; Petition for Withholding theses (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - NAS General Synthetic Methods and New Reagents, e.g. Collins reagent (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Corticoid Side-Chain Methods of Synthesis (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cortisone acetate (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Total Synthesis of Corticoids: Johnson, Nakamura, Slovik (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, reports, typescripts, articles, symposium program (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Iso-butyenyl Experimental section (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Final report info (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Bernardo H. II (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bernardo H. I (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Slides (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Hshiou-Ting Liu (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Final Report (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Bound volumes of William S. Johnson and Associates Publications: 1943-1947; 1948-1953; 1954-1961; 1962-1965; 1966-1974. (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Bound volumes of William S. Johnson and Associates Publications: 1966-1975; 1976-1985. (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Misc. correspondence., abstracts, papers, reprints (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - NIH renewal 1989 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Lee (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Kuder, Margie (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Accounting (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Renovations (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Financial Authority (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Blanket Accounts (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Cylinder Rental (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Transfer (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - On-line Purchasing (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Off-line Purchasing (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lai (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Stuff (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Paul Fish (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - On-line Invoice-Paying (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Post Docs (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Brandstadter (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Jones (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Rajapaksa (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Sen (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Singam (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Vuligonda (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Postdoc Applications--No (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Apple Computers (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Budget Information (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Expenditure Statement 5/31/92 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Expenditure Statement 4/30/92 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Expenditure Statement 3/31/92 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Expenditure Statement 2/29/92 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Expenditure Statement 1/31/92 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Expenditure Statement 12/31/91 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Expenditure Statement 11/31/91 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Expenditure Statement 10/31/91 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Expenditure Statement 9/30/91 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Expenditure Statement 8/30/91 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - 1 FBB 102 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Budget Statements--Investments (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - 2 FBB 609 Sterling Winthrop (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - 2 FBB 410 GM-04 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Research Group (Misc. Information) (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Equipment (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - RPO's--Miscellaneous (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Mass Spec - UCSF (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Hewlett Packard Recorder (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Journal of the American Chemistry Society - Referee '59 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Journal of Organic Chemistry - Referee (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Miscellaneous Journals - Referee (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Reviews - Proposals (Miscellaneous) (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Physiology Tests and Sample Requests '65- (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Requests for Information/Services (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Tetrahedron - Referee (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Tetrahedron Letters - Referee (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - NIH AM 03787-26 (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - NIH AM 03787-27 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - NIH DK 03787-29 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - NSF--12/1/86 - 11/30/87 (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - Office Memoranda (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - References--Grad Students (Box 18, Folder 40)
  - Copyright Transfer Forms (Box 18, Folder 41)
  - SAF's (Student appointments)--Current (Box 18, Folder 42)
  - NIH Supply Account (Box 18, Folder 43)
  - NIH-35 (Box 18, Folder 44)
  - NIH Renewal (Box 18, Folder 45)
  - Info Sheet--Former Collaborators (Box 18, Folder 46)
  - NIH DK 03787-28 (Box 18, Folder 47)
  - Johnson Symposium--1989 Master List (Non-Collaborators) (Box 18, Folder 48)
  - Johnson Symposium--1989 Master List (Collaborators) (Box 18, Folder 49)
  - NIH DK 03787-30 (Box 18, Folder 50)
  - RPO's--Analyses and CAS On-Line (Box 18, Folder 51)
  - No-'94 (Box 18, Folder 52)
  - Aldrich Chemical Company 602 (Box 18, Folder 53)
  - Postdoc Forms (Box 18, Folder 54)
  - Budget Statements 2FBB612 Lilly, Eli (Box 18, Folder 55)
  - Postdoc Applications--Active (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - NSF 1992 (Box 18, Folder 57)
  - Pfizer, Inc.--Grant (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Smith Kline Beecham (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - NSF--Progress Reports (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Abrams, G. D. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Ackerman, James H. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Allen, Charles F. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Allen, Duff S. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Andrew, Robert G. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Andrews, Glenn C. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Arnold, Robert A. (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Bailey, Denis M. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Banerjee, D. K. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Bannister, Brian (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Bartlett, Paul A. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Bartlett, William R. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Bartmann, Wilhelm (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Bass, John D. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Bauer, Victor J. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Bayliss, Geoffrey S. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Becker, Dan (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Belew, John S. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Bell, Russell A. (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Berner, Daniel (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Bhattacharyya, Bidyut K. (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Biellmann, Jean-Francois (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Birkeland, Stephen P. (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Bloom, Barry M. (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Gray, Sharon L. (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Brady, Stephen F. (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Brandstadter, Stephan M. (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Brinkmeyer, Raymond S. (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Brocksom, Timothy J. (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Brot, Frederick E. (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Brown, Morris (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Bruya, Jim (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Bryson, Thomas A. (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Buchanan, Robert A. (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Bull, James R. (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Bunes, Leonard A. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Burckhardt, Urs (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Calzada, José (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Campbell, Simon F. (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Cannon, Carolyn A. (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Maeda, Janet Carlson (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Carney, Robert L. (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Chan, Ming Fai (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Chenera, Balan (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Chen Yu-qun (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Cheng, Soan (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Chinn, Leland J. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Choi, Vanessa (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Cheung, Yak-Fa (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Christiansen, Robert (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Clement, Robert A. (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Cohen, Noal (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Cole, John E. (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Collins, Joseph C. (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Conklin, Edward J. (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Conrow, Raymond E. (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Coverdale, Charles E. (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Cox, John M. (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Crackett, Peter H. (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Craddock, Henry A. (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Crandall, Jack K. (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Crawford, Robert J. (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Crosby, Guy A. (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - Darling, Stephen D. (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Daub, Guido H. (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Daub, G. William (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - David, Israel A. (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Davis, Chester E. (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - DeAcetis, William (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - De Jongh, Hendrik, A. P. (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Dehm, Henry C. (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Della, Ernest W. (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Demnitz, John (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Dickie, J. P. (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Dolak, Lester A. (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Dominguez, Jose N. (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Doshan, Harold (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Dubas, Lawrence F. (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - DuBois, Grant E. (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Dumas, Donald J. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Dunathan, Harmon C. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Dutta, Jadu (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Eade, Ronald A. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Eastham, Jerome F. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Edington, Clare (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Eggelte, T. A. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Elliott, John D. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Elliott, Ray (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Eswarakrishnan, Seetha (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Escher, Sina (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Fagundo, Carmen R. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Faulkner, D. John (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Fedoruk, N. A. (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Finn, Robert G. (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Fish, Robert A. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Fitzi, Konrad (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Fletcher, Vernon R. (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Fonken, Gerhard J. (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Franck, Richard W. (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Frei, Bruno (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Fung, Victor A. (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Ganem, Bruce (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Gao, Yun (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Garst, Michael E. (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Gastambide, Bernard (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Gelotte, Karl O. (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Giarrsso, Fred F. (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Glenn, Howard J. (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Gopalan, Aravamudan S. (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Graham, Donald W. (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Gravestock, Michael B. (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Guay, Daniel (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Gutsche, C. David (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Haag, William G., Jr. (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Habicht, Ernst (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Hadler, Herbert I. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Hall, Horace Thompson (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Hahn, Roger C. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Hamilton, Carole L. (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Hamon, David (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Hanson, Gunnar (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Harbert, Charles A. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Harding, Kenn E. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Harsy, Steve (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Hendrick, Michael E. (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Herradon, Bernado (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Herrin, Thomas (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Hirschmann, Ralph F. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Hobbs, Frank W., Jr. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Hooz, John (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Hudrlik, Anne M. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Hudrlik, Paul F. (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Huesmann, Peter L. (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Huffman, William F. (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Hughes, L. R. (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Hunter, Norman R. (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Huntrakul, Charus (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Hussein, Ahmad Q. (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Ilton, Marcia A. (Dawson) (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Ireland, Robert E. (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Jagodzinski, Jacek J. (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - James, Keith (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Jaques, Brian (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Jeffay, Henry (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Jensen, Norman P. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Johns, William F. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Jones, A. Russell (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Jones, Evan T. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Jones, Fran (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Jordan, Lawrence M. (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Kallos, John (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Kapoor, Vijaya M. (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Katner, Allen S. (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Keana, John F. W. (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Kellog, Michael S. (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Kelson, Andrew B. (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Kemp, Alex D. (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Kertesz, Denis J. (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Kikuchi, Katsuo (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Kinnel, Robin B. (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Kloek, James A. (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Kloss, Robert A. (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Kobal, Val M. (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Korst, James J. (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Kreutzer, Armin (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Kropp, Paul J. (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Labovitz, Jeffrey (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Lago, M. Amparo (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Lazar, Joseph (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Lemaire, Henry C. (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Leopold, Eric (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Lewis, Arthur J. (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Li, Tsung-Tee (Fred) (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Li, Ying (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Lindell, Stephen (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Liu, Hshiou-ting (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Livinghouse, Tom S. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Loew, Peter (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lowe, John (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lunn, William H. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lyle, Terry A. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - McCarry, Brian E. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - McCloskey, Allen L. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Macdonald, Timothy (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Manatt, Stanley L. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Markezich, Ronald L. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Marlowe, Charles (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Marshall, James A. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Martin, David G. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Massanet, G. M. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Metcalf, B. W. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Metler, Thomas J. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Meyer, Walter L. (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Miles, D. Howard (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Miller, Max W. (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Molloy, Bryan B. (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Moloney, Brian A. (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Morton, Douglas R., Jr. (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Moyer, Patricia H. (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Muller, Robert Karl (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Myers, Robert F. (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Nabney, John (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Natarajan, S. (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Nederlof, Peter (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Neeman, Moshe (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Neustaedter, Pedro J. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Newton, Clive (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Niem, Tony (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Niwa, Mineo (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Ohki, Eiji (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Okorie, D. A. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Olson, Gary (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Okuda, Shigenobu (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Owyang, Raymond (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Pappo, Raphael (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Parker, Kathlyn A. (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Parry, Ronald J. (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Pedrosa, Rafael (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Perryman, Edwin L. (Lab. Assistant) (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Petersen, Jack W. (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Phillips, Donald K. (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Pietruszewski, Cornel (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Pike, John E. (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Plummer, Mark S. (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Prestwich, Glenn D. (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Ramazani, Said (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Rasmusson, Gary H. (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Rabold, Gary (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Rapala, Richard T. (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Ratcliffe, Bruce E. (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Ravelo, Angel G. (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Rich, Daniel H. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Richter, Peter (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Rizzi, George P. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Roberts, Bryan (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Roberts, John Paul (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Roblin, Richard (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Ronald, Robert C. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Rubin, Mordecai B. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Saiz, Pilar (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Sargent, G. Dann (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Schaaf, Thomas K. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Schiess, Peter W. (Box 26, Folder 12)